{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Cabinet Repair Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40004/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40004,"taskName":"Cabinets - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair Cabinets","xmTaskDescriptor":"Cabinet Repair Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":32,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Cabinet vanity storage pantry cabinetry","textMessagingName":"Repr Cabinets","rolloverLongDesc":"Cabinets typically go out of style long before they wear out.  Alternatives to replacement include repainting, installing new hardware or having them refaced.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes broken hinges, loose doors, faulty drawers.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Cabinets.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Cabinet Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Kitchen Cabinets, Cabinet Drawers \u0026 Doors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Cabinet Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Cabinets - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Cabinet Repair Project","urlName":"Cabinets-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Cabinet Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen Cabinets, Doors \u0026 Drawers","searchKeywords":"Cabinet,vanity,storage,pantry,cabinetry,bathroom,kitchen,basement,garage,cupboards","emcCategoryOid":-12009,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":328,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40004/":{"taskOID":40004,"originalTaskOID":40004,"setID":328,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":323,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Check all problems you are having with your cabinets.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shelves are sagging or broken","answerDisplayText":"Shelves are sagging or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2082,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drawers do not glide smoothly","answerDisplayText":"Drawers do not glide smoothly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken bottom","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2081,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken guide","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken guide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2080,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken front","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken front","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2016,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Door is warped","answerDisplayText":"Door is warped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3017,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Hinge is broken","answerDisplayText":"Hinge is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":324,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinet Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material are the cabinets made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3441,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":323,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Check all problems you are having with your cabinets.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shelves are sagging or broken","answerDisplayText":"Shelves are sagging or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2082,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drawers do not glide smoothly","answerDisplayText":"Drawers do not glide smoothly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken bottom","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2081,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken guide","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken guide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2080,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken front","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken front","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2016,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Door is warped","answerDisplayText":"Door is warped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3017,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Hinge is broken","answerDisplayText":"Hinge is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5635,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Shelves are sagging or broken","answerDisplayText":"Shelves are sagging or broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2082,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Drawers do not glide smoothly","answerDisplayText":"Drawers do not glide smoothly","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2079,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken bottom","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken bottom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2081,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken guide","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken guide","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2080,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Drawer has a broken front","answerDisplayText":"Drawer has a broken front","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2016,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Door is warped","answerDisplayText":"Door is warped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3017,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Hinge is broken","answerDisplayText":"Hinge is broken","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":324,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinet Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material are the cabinets made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3441,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3441,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}